(Raj:)You said I could
buy a desk.
This isn't a desk.
(Sheldon:)This is a...
Brobdingnagian
monstrosity.
(Raj:)Is that the American idiom
for "giant, big-ass desk"?
(Sheldon:)It's actually British.
(Raj:)Can you say it again for me?
(Sheldon:)Brobdingnagian.
(Raj:)One more time?
(Raj:)Now three times fast?
(Sheldon:)Brobdingnagian, Brobdingna...
(Sheldon:)How did you even
get it in here?
(Raj:)That's for me, Ramon, Julio,
Jesus and Rodrigo to know
(Raj:)and you to find out.
(Sheldon:)All right, you've
made your point.
(Sheldon:)A fine prank, very amusing.
(Sheldon:)Now get it out.
(Raj:)No.
(Sheldon:)Yes.
No.
Yes!
I have three brothers
(Raj:)and two sisters, Sheldon--
I can do this all day.
(Sheldon:)All right, if you're
not going to remove it,
(Sheldon:)I'll remove it for you.